[A Mission of the Heart]
[مهمة القلب]
[Episode 3]
[الحلقة 3]
[Northern Inspection Division]
[قسم التفتيش الشمالي]
My Lord, you're suspicious of Ms. Huang.
سيدي، أنت تشك في السيدة هوانغ.
Why do you still try to recruit her to the division?
لماذا لا تزال تحاول تجنيدها للقسم؟
Although she's not off suspicion yet,
على الرغم من أنها لم تخرج من دائرة الشك بعد،
she's somewhat competent.
إنها كفؤة إلى حد ما.
It's better to keep such a person nearby.
من الأفضل إبقاء مثل هذا الشخص قريبًا.
We need to work out a way
نحن بحاجة إلى إيجاد طريقة
to make her willingly join the Northern Inspection Division.
لجعلها تنضم طوعا إلى قسم التفتيش الشمالي.
What about a ruse of self-injury?
ماذا عن خدعة إيذاء النفس؟
Who is it?
من هذا؟
My Lord?
سيدي؟
What?
ماذا؟
You're asking me to pay ten taels a month for his medical expenses?
أنت تطلب مني أن أدفع له عشرة تايل شهريًا لتغطية نفقاته الطبية؟
But he's not so severely injured
ولكنه لم يتعرض لإصابة خطيرة
that he needs 10 taels a month for medical treatment, is he?
أنه يحتاج إلى 10 تايل شهريا للعلاج، أليس كذلك؟
It takes that much for Zhao to recover.
يحتاج تشاو إلى هذا القدر من أجل التعافي.
My Lord,
سيدي
I only suggested a ruse of self-injury,
لقد اقترحت فقط خدعة إيذاء النفس،
not extortion!
لا ابتزاز!
My Lord,
سيدي
you've seen my humble abode.
لقد رأيت مسكني المتواضع.
Even if I work day and night without food or rest,
حتى لو عملت ليلًا ونهارًا دون طعام أو راحة،
I still won't be able to pay that much money.
لن أكون قادرًا على دفع هذا القدر من المال.
Considering that I helped you catch a criminal,
بالنظر إلى أنني ساعدتك في القبض على مجرم،
could you reduce the amount?
هل بإمكانك تقليل المبلغ؟
I suppose I could.
أعتقد أنني أستطيع.
However,
لكن،
my mercy is only reserved for those who work for me.
رحمتي مخصصة فقط لأولئك الذين يعملون لدي.
Now, his real purpose is revealed.
والآن تم الكشف عن هدفه الحقيقي.
Well,
حسنًا،
Ms. Huang, have you made a decision yet?
السيدة هوانغ، هل اتخذت قرارًا بعد؟
Yes, I have.
نعم لدي.
It's my honor
إنه شرف لي
to work for you, My Lord.
للعمل لديك يا سيدي.
[Zhao Mansion]
[قصر تشاو]
Lord Shen, why did you come to my place instead of working the case
يا سيد شين، لماذا أتيت إلى مكاني بدلاً من العمل على القضية؟
and hunting after the murderer?
ومطاردة القاتل؟
Being confused about something,
الارتباك بشأن شيء ما،
I specially came to consult you, Lord Zhao.
لقد أتيت خصيصا لاستشارتك، يا سيد تشاو.
What is the matter?
ما المشكلة؟
The murderer is said to
ويقال أن القاتل
only target the brides of ghost marriages who died unnatural deaths.
استهدف فقط عرائس الزيجات الشبحية اللاتي ماتوا موتًا غير طبيعي.
Shen Pan, what are you implying?
شين بان، ماذا تقصد؟
That I killed that bride?
أنني قتلت تلك العروسة؟
Did you not?
ألم تفعل؟
Zhao Ming!
تشاو مينغ!
Master.
يتقن.
Where did you find that bride for Wenshu?
أين وجدت تلك العروس لـوينشو؟
Master,
يتقن،
she was introduced by Madam Wang the matchmaker.
تم تقديمها من قبل السيدة وانج الخاطبة.
How did the bride die?
كيف ماتت العروسة؟
According to Madam Wang, she died of illness.
وبحسب السيدة وانغ، فإنها توفيت بسبب المرض.
She died of illness at such a young age?
لقد ماتت بسبب المرض في مثل هذا العمر الصغير؟
Yes.
نعم.
I didn't give it too much thought back then.
لم أفكر في الأمر كثيرًا في ذلك الوقت.
Since the time of her birth was astrologically
منذ أن كان وقت ولادتها فلكيًا
compatible with the young master's,
متوافق مع السيد الشاب،
I arranged a ghost marriage for them.
لقد رتبت لهم زواجًا شبحيًا.
Lord Shen, do you have other questions?
سيد شين، هل لديك أسئلة أخرى؟
No, not for now.
لا، ليس في الوقت الراهن.
I'm afraid I may have to
أخشى أن أضطر إلى ذلك
come and trouble you again if there are new questions.
سأعود وأزعجك مرة أخرى إذا كانت هناك أسئلة جديدة.
Zhao Ming,
تشاو مينغ,
Lord Shen's tea has gone cold. Replace it now.
شاي اللورد شين برد. استبدله الآن.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I'll take my leave now.
سوف آخذ إجازتي الآن.
Show Lord Shen out.
أظهر اللورد شين.
Lord Shen, this way, please.
يا سيد شين، من هنا من فضلك.
Fresh vegetables!
خضروات طازجة!
Candied haws on a stick!
الزعرور المسكر على عصا!
Come take a look!
تعالوا وانظروا!
Have you not found the Qiao family yet?
هل لم تجد عائلة تشياو بعد؟
No.
لا.
Continue the search then.
واصل البحث إذن.
Also, look for Madam Wang.
ابحث أيضًا عن السيدة وانج.
Yes.
نعم.
My Lord,
سيدي
isn't that Lord Lu and Ms. Huang?
أليس هذا هو اللورد لو والسيدة هوانغ؟
Could there be something going on between them?
هل يمكن أن يكون هناك شيء يحدث بينهما؟
Don't you have better things to do?
هل ليس لديك أشياء أفضل للقيام بها؟
Get back to work!
العودة إلى العمل!
Yes, sure.
نعم بالتأكيد.
Lord Shen!
اللورد شين!
Yu, what are you doing here?
يو ماذا تفعل هنا؟
Any findings?
أي نتائج؟
Zhao Yutang said Qiao Pan'er died of illness.
قال تشاو يوتانغ أن تشياو بان إير توفيت بسبب المرض.
If that were true,
لو كان ذلك صحيحا،
why would the Qiao family have run away?
لماذا هربت عائلة تشياو؟
Too bad that the entire Qiao family has fled.
من المؤسف أن عائلة تشياو بأكملها قد هربت.
I wonder if Madam Wang the matchmaker
أتساءل عما إذا كانت السيدة وانغ هي الخاطبة
is still still alive.
لا يزال على قيد الحياة.
The Zhao Mansion is large.
قصر تشاو كبير.
I'm sure someone there will slip and say something.
أنا متأكد من أن شخصًا ما هناك سوف يتسلل ويقول شيئًا.
Why are you looking at me?
لماذا تنظر إلي؟
There are many women in the Zhao Mansion.
هناك العديد من النساء في قصر تشاو.
Getting some facts from them
الحصول على بعض الحقائق منهم
won't be difficult for you,
لن يكون الأمر صعبًا عليك،
right, Lord Shen?
يمينًا، يا سيد شين؟
That's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
Lord Lu,
اللورد لو،
how can I hold a candle
كيف يمكنني أن أحمل شمعة؟
to a devastatingly handsome man
إلى رجل وسيم بشكل مدمر
such as yourself?
مثل نفسك؟
Spill it.
انسكبه.
How did Qiao Pan'er die?
كيف ماتت تشياو بان إير؟
Could you tell me
هل يمكنك أن تخبرني
I don't know how she died.
لا أعرف كيف ماتت.
But I know how I'm going to die.
ولكنني أعلم كيف سأموت.
Am I really that handsome?
هل أنا حقا وسيم إلى هذه الدرجة؟
My Lord,
سيدي
I think we can
أعتقد أننا نستطيع
adopt certain tactics.
إتباع تكتيكات معينة.
Nonetheless,
ومع ذلك،
we need an elegant gentleman like Lord Shen
نحن بحاجة إلى رجل أنيق مثل اللورد شين
to carry out the plan.
لتنفيذ الخطة.
Really?
حقًا؟
Really.
حقًا.
After all, most women
بعد كل شيء، معظم النساء
would be disarmed and flustered
سيكون منزوع السلاح ومضطربًا
by Lord Shen's charm.
بفضل سحر اللورد شين.
Are you
أنت
one of those women, Yu?
واحدة من هؤلاء النساء، يو؟
Fine.
بخير.
Given all those glowing terms Yu spoke of me,
بالنظر إلى كل تلك المصطلحات المتوهجة التي تحدث عنها يو عني،
I have no option but to humbly accept the task.
ليس لدي خيار سوى قبول المهمة بتواضع.
Tomorrow,
غداً،
just wait till I bring good news to you.
فقط انتظر حتى أحمل لك أخبارًا جيدة.
Officer Huang,
الضابط هوانغ،
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
Go buy me some fruits and snacks.
اذهب واشتري لي بعض الفواكه والوجبات الخفيفة.
Why are you staring at me?
لماذا تحدق بي؟
This is usually Zhao's job.
هذه هي وظيفة تشاو عادةً.
But since he's injured now,
ولكن بما أنه مصاب الآن،
you'll have to do it in his stead.
سيتعين عليك القيام بذلك بدلاً منه.
Don't spend too much.
لا تنفق الكثير.
Sir,
سيد،
I'll take all the fried flatbreads.
سوف آخذ كل الخبز المسطح المقلي.
Yes, miss.
نعم يا آنسة.
Make it quick. I'll come get them later.
افعل ذلك بسرعة. سآتي لأخذهم لاحقًا.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll take six steamed meant buns.
سوف آخذ ستة كعكات مطهوة على البخار.
Here's the money. I'll come get them later.
ها هي الأموال، سآتي لأخذها لاحقًا.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
I'll take two of each then.
سوف آخذ اثنين من كل نوع إذن.
I'll come get them later.
سوف آتي لأخذهم لاحقًا.
Here you are.
تفضل.
Miss, the steamed buns are ready!
آنسة، الكعك المطهو ​​على البخار جاهز!
Thank you, sir.
شكرا لك سيدي.
Coming right up!
قادمة في الحال!
Put them in my bag.
ضعهم في حقيبتي.
Okay.
تمام.
Thank you, sir.
شكرا لك سيدي.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Why so clumsy, Officer Huang?
لماذا هذا الإهمال يا ضابط هوانغ؟
Listen,
يستمع،
you'll pay for them with your salary if they're damaged.
سوف تدفع ثمنها من راتبك إذا تعرضت للتلف.
Eat up.
تناول الطعام.
Lord Lu,
اللورد لو،
what else can I do for you?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل لك أيضًا؟
Nothing for now.
لا شيء حتى الآن.
Lord Lu.
اللورد لو.
Ms. Huang.
السيدة هوانغ.
Lord Shen has gone to the Zhao Mansion for inquiries.
ذهب اللورد شين إلى قصر تشاو للاستفسار.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
I found the Qiao family.
لقد وجدت عائلة تشياو.
However...
لكن...
Something happened?
هل حدث شيء؟
It has the same smell as the incense found at the scene of Zhao Wenshu's case.
إنها تحمل نفس رائحة البخور الذي وجد في مكان قضية تشاو وينشو.
Why did the murderer strike when the incense was only half burned?
لماذا ضرب القاتل عندما كان البخور محترقا إلى النصف فقط؟
My Lord,
سيدي
I think
أظن
the three victims were all arranged
تم ترتيب الضحايا الثلاثة جميعًا
in kneeling positions after they died.
في وضع الركوع بعد وفاتهم.
The murderer has more hatred
القاتل لديه المزيد من الكراهية
for Qiao Pan'er's family than for Zhao Wenshu.
لعائلة Qiao Pan'er أكثر من Zhao Wenshu.
The murderer meant to make them repent.
وكان القاتل يقصد أن يجعلهم يتوبون.
Qiao Pan'er didn't die of illness.
لم تمت تشياو بان إير بسبب المرض.
If they hadn't been greedy for money,
لو لم يكونوا جشعين للمال،
they might have escaped death.
ربما نجوا من الموت.
That said, these people got what they deserved.
ومع ذلك، فقد حصل هؤلاء الأشخاص على ما يستحقونه.
In a sense, the murderer did a good thing.
بمعنى ما، لقد فعل القاتل شيئًا جيدًا.
Judge the deed, not the thought.
احكم على الفعل، وليس على الفكرة.
No justifiable cause can deny the fact
لا يوجد سبب مبرر يمكن أن ينكر الحقيقة
that the murderer did wrong.
أن القاتل أخطأ.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I guess
اعتقد
Shen Pan has had new discoveries by now.
لقد اكتشف شين بان أشياء جديدة حتى الآن.
Mao,
لذا،
bring the bodies to the Ministry of Punishments.
نقل الجثث إلى وزارة العقوبات.
Yes.
نعم.